Finding Aid for Sesquicentennial Office (University of Michigan) records, 1959-1967
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs: Sesquicentennial events and office staff. Phil Davis Sesquicentennial Exhibition
  - Photographs
    - Contact prints, photos taken for exhibition, 28 folders
      - R.F. experiment, physics: Forester in tree. Physics student assembling copper ring coil., 36 frames; 178 (Box 13)
      - Dr. Vonbaumparten with sea slugs. August [Physics Machine Shop]. Prisoners Dilemma. Goldfish. [?] choir chamber., 36 frames; 179 (Box 13)
      - Monkey, bearing research-N.G. Dr. Sam Barnes, Army lecture. Construction. Girls' orientation group, 36 frames; 180 (Box 13)
      - Guitarist and girl friend. M. M. Brown at Hill organ (3 are 56mm), 15 frames; 181 (Box 13)
      - Pretzel Bell, 36 frames; 182 (Box 13)
      - [not received], 183 (Box 13)
      - W. A. running shots, 30 frames; 184 (Box 13)
      - Interlochen counselors ed. Shell rehearsal. Rain. Junior violinist, 36 frames; 185 (Box 13)
      - Interlochen orchestra rehearsal. Photographer in bowl, 36 frames; 186 (Box 13)
      - Interlochen 2475-Shell rehearsal-Kresge, 36 frames; 187 (Box 13)
      - Interlochen-concert and awards in Bowl N.G. (56mm), 12 frames; 188 (Box 13)
      - Interlochen-Band bowl rehearsal-behind bass, horns (56mm), 12 frames; 189 (Box 13)
      - Interlochen-pre-rehearsal in Kresge-tuning tympani (56mm), 12 frames; 190 (Box 13)
      - Interlochen students, general, 34 frames; 191 (Box 13)
      - Interlochen pre-rehearsal and instrument repairman (56m-), 12 frames; 192 (Box 13)
      - Maynard Klein, 32 frames; 193 (Box 13)
      - Interloch,7~n-viola lesson, tent theater, 36 frames; 194 (Box 13)
      - Interlochen dancers.-Rehearsal in bowl, 30 frames; 195 (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails-speech therapist in woods; kids looking at Hasselblad (56mm), 12 frames; 196 (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails outdoor counseling (56mm), 12 frames; 197 (Box 13)
      - Speech Camp-little kids, outdoor therapy; also older kids through trees, 34 frames; 198 (Box 13)
      - Speech counseling in woods and on beach through trees (56mm), 12 frames; 199 (Box 13)
      - Speech camp-round robin and mail, 40 frames; 200 (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails-speech therapist on beach; boy speaking at lectern in woods, 36 frames; 201 (Box 13)
      - Speech Camp-mail; announcements; cabin practice for round robin, 35 frames; 202 (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails-counseling in woods, on beach and checker game (56mm), 12 frames; 203 (Box 13)
      - Speech Camp-baseball, waterfront, checker game (56mm), 12 frames; 204 (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails-fishing and swimming, 36 frames; 205 (Box 13)
      - Shady Trails-fishing. Forestry-saw filing, 34 frames; 206 (Box 13)
      - Forestry-soil check; log rolling, match splitting, 36 frames; 207 (Box 13)
      - Forestry-Tool room; burling, 36 frames; 208 (Box 13)
      - Forestry -- classroom; tool room; burling (56mm), 12 frames; 209 (Box 13)
      - Forestry-store-office (56mm), 12 frames; 210 (Box 13)
      - Forestry Camp-Store and mess hall, 36 frames; 211 (Box 13)
      - Forestry Camp-Classroom, evening. Also geology classroom, Jim McClurg, 36 frames; 212 (Box 13)
      - Forestry Camp-Mensuration Woods, 36 frames; 213 (Box 13)
      - Forestry Measurement; office. Geology, 35 frames; 214 (Box 13)
      - Geology Mapping field trip-plus X, 36 frames; 215 (Box 13)
      - [Geology]-Steg and Marty; Jim McClurg in classroom, 36 frames; 216 (Box 13)
      - Geology-Ike Smith and kids checking aerial maps-, 34 frames; 217 (Box 13)
      - Geology-Mapping, Ike Smith; campfire (56mm), 11 frames; 218 (Box 13)
      - Camp Davis from mountain (56mm), 12 frames; 219 (Box 13)
      - Geology-Surveyors on mountain (56mm), 12 frames; 220 (Box 13)
      - Geology-Bill Kelly and kids, field trip. Also Jim McClurg, 36 frames; 221 (Box 13)
      - Geology-Campfire; Lucy in kitchen; dining hall, 36 frames; 222 (Box 13)
      - Geology -- Stege[?], Lucy and preparation for mapping trip. Also Bill Kelly and rock samples, 36 frames; 223 (Box 13)
      - Bill Kelly-gold panning, 38 frames; 224 (Box 13)
      - Geology-dining hall, Lucy. [Paleontology]-Hibbard and student in camp, 33 frames; 225 (Box 13)
      - Dr. Hibbard and grad student at site., 38 frames; 226 (Box 13)
      - Hibbard and grad student at site (56mm), 12 frames; 227 (Box 13)
      - Mt. Evans-1st roll Dr. Lawrence Jones (56mm), 12 frames; 228 (Box 13)
      - On top of Mt. Evans 2nd roll (56mm), 12 frames; 229 (Box 13)
      - Kim (56mm) 3, 230 (Box 13)
      - Leslie White (56nm), 12 frames; 231-232 (Box 13)
      - Leslie White; Manupelli [George -- art professor?], 18 frames; 233 (Box 13)
      - Losh, 36 frames; 234-235 (Box 13)
      - Stanley Quartet, Rackham. Students registering in Greene House, 36 frames; 236 (Box 13)
      - Student registering in dorm. Football practice, 36 frames; 237 (Box 13)
      - Greene House-2475-Students entering, 36 frames; 238 (Box 13)
      - Signing in East Quad. Football practice, 36 frames; 239 (Box 13)
      - East Quad and registration [moving in], 33 frames; 240 (Box 13)
      - Coming in-East Quad, 34 frames; 241 (Box 13)
      - Vocational Therapy-shoe maker., 38 frames; 242 (Box 13)
      - Occupational Therapy. East Quad, 35 frames; 243 (Box 13)
      - Jim Hurt, football. Appliances, 36 frames; 244 (Box 13)
      - Registration-paper on ground, and in Waterman, 38 frames; 245 (Box 13)
      - Registration-telephoto shots (56mm), 12 frames; 246 (Box 13)
      - Registration-looking down on fluorescent lights (56mm), 12 frames; 247 (Box 13)
      - Registration; girls sitting on floor (56mm), 12 frames; 248 (Box 13)
      - Registration-Plus X, 36 frames; 249 (Box 13)
      - Band marching to pep rally, and rally at Rackham, 36 frames; 250 (Box 13)
      - Pep rally and sing, Rackham 2475, 33 frames; 251 (Box 13)
      - Book buying. Sam. Window. History plaque, 23 frames; 252 (Box 13)
      - Nurses, window shots, 36 frames; 253 (Box 13)
      - Nurses-nothing roll, 36 frames; 254 (Box 13)
      - Swimming and gymnastics, 36 frames; 255-256 (Box 13)
      - Gymnastics, 36 frames; 257 (Box 13)
      - Nurses. Gym parallel bars, 36 frames; 258 (Box 13)
      - Jim Hunt [head trainer-taping a knee], 36 frames; 259 (Box 13)
      - Football practice. Baseball telephoto, 35 frames; 260 (Box 13)
      - Football and baseball, Hasselblad (56mm), 16 frames; 261 (Box 13)
      - Football practice-500mm lens (56mm), 16 frames; 262 (Box 13)
      - Sport parachute, motorcycle, Eccentrics, sailing club, 30 frames; 263 (Box 13)
      - Marching Band practice. Nurses, 36 frames; 264 (Box 13)
      - Football team dressing, 36 frames; 265 (Box 13)
      - Football-pre-game warmup -- Revelli [band director], 38 frames; 266 (Box 13)
      - Band formation on field. Players standing at bench, 36 frames; 267 (Box 13)
      - Bandsmen and coaches at bench, 36 frames; 268 (Box 13)
      - Band and crowd at football game, 36 frames; 269 (Box 13)
      - Nurses-nutrition. Super Wide lens (56mm), 12 frames; 270 (Box 13)
      - Nurses-class in nutrition. Rollei (56mm), 12 frames; 271 (Box 13)
      - Nurses-tasting. Rollei (56mm), 12 frames; 272 (Box 13)
      - TV studio. Music School building (56mm), 12 frames; 273 (Box 13)
      - Baroque Trio (56mm), 12 frames; 274 (Box 13)
      - Baroque Trio (56mm) 8, 275 (Box 13)
      - Baroque Trio. Daily editors. (56mm), 12 frames; 276 (Box 13)
      - Pep rally (56mm), 16 frames; 277 (Box 13)
      - Football-running players, blurred (56mm), 16 frames; 278 (Box 13)
      - Building Homecoming displays 2475, 36 frames; 279 (Box 13)
      - Hatcher tea-flash Leica, 36 frames; 280 (Box 13)
      - Hatcher tea-Nikon, 36 frames; 281 (Box 13)
      - Galens, campus in snow, 22 frames; 282 (Box 13)
      - Galens, near Hill Auditorium (56mm), 12 frames; 283 (Box 13)
      - Galens sign at crossing (56wn), 12 frames; 284 (Box 13)
      - Galens sign, no. 2 (56mm), 12 frames; 285 (Box 13)
- Negatives
  - Exhibition negatives (Box 14)
    (negatives arranged by number corresponding to contact sheet number.)
    Restricted: Staff use only